My thought is
to go for it,
and go big.
I want to invite more friends over.
After the ceremony,
we can throw
a huge party.
It'll be great for everyone
to drink and have fun together.
Right.
I've already checked with them.
They'll fly back from abroad.
We just need
to set aside time
in advance to arrange it.
Then everything is
all set.
Leave the rest
to me.
Thank you, Mr. Gao.
Thanks, Dad.
Nanny.
Get the car ready.
Okay.
You two keep eating.
I'll walk you out.
Dad,
it's raining outside.
How about you don't visit Mom today.
Go tomorrow morning when it clears up.
Rain or shine.
A little rain
is nothing.
Yanyan
is looking out for her dad.
She's grown up.
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
I just wanted to...
Wanted to what?
Don't even think about it.
Go back to your own house.
Auntie Wu, see him out.
The old man goes to
the old residence on time.
The closely watched Typhoon Megi
swept across Luzon Island
in the Philippines a week ago.
...and is heading straight
for our Motor City.
Although it has weakened significantly,
it will still bring heavy wind and rain.
Zhao,
turn it off.
Yes, Mr. Gao.
Mr. Gao, maybe
we shouldn't go.
The radio said
there's extreme weather tonight,
a once-in-a-decade event.
It's been 30 years.
I've never missed it.
How about I drop you off
when we get there?
No need.
I drew a box
and made a waterproof mark,
right next to that tree.
You just need to park the tricycle
inside that box.
Hello,
the vehicle is parked.
But this positioning box you drew,
won't it be discovered later?
Don't worry.
Someone will clean it up.
Find a quiet place to hide
and report to me at any time.
What's the situation on your end?
I guess
Gao Yuhai is almost there.
I've arrived,
but it seems a car has been following me.
Don't worry.
Take it easy.
I have my own arrangements for the rest.
Why does this car look so familiar?
It can't be.
Who would be so bored
to put it here?
No.
These dents,
this model...
Do you understand?
Can Shen Xi do it?
Will there be any mistakes?
Very likely.
If he doesn't die from the first hit,
you follow up
and hit him again.
Do you dare?
For Shen Xi,
I do.
That old bastard
is worse than a beast. He deserves to die.
What if he doesn't die
from the first hit?
Then we'll see
where he's injured first.
I've read a lot of books on this recently.
I should be able to handle it.
For bullying Shen Xi,
he must die.
He must die.
If everything goes smoothly
and Gao Yuhai is killed in one hit,
remember
the box I drew.
You're responsible for
cleaning up the scene.
Understand?
Understood.
Save me.
I remember now.
You're the one who gave me the toy.
Yes, I even took you
to the amusement park.
Xiao Si,
say hi to Uncle Gao.
Say it.
This is...
My son.
He's grown so tall.
A bit shy with strangers, too.
Shy, yes.
I just
checked,
and Jiuzhou's condition is stable.
He was rescued in time.
Let him get a good sleep.
Zhao Wenjuan.
I have other things
to attend to at the group,
so I'll head back first.
If you have any difficulties
in the future,
come to me anytime.
I'll walk you out.
That's right.
I am Bai Jiuzhou's son.
Bai Xiaosi!
He kidnapped me,
threatened my dad
to commit perjury for him,
and killed Song Yanfei's dad.
Then he sent Feng Shu
to stage a traffic accident
to kill my dad,
leaving no witnesses.
My dad was lucky
and survived.
He even went to the hospital
to finish him off.
Officer,
isn't he guilty of heinous crimes?
Doesn't he deserve it?
Doesn't he deserve to die?
You should seek legal help
instead of fighting
violence with violence.
Understand? You're still a kid.
Would that even work?
My mom stayed with him
for so many years despite her disgust.
Why?
Wasn't it just for the evidence?
He's rich and powerful.
What else could a widow and her child
do?
There's nothing we can do.
Mr. Feng,
Feng Shu!
You're finally
here.
The recent death of Gao Yuhai,
a prominent local entrepreneur,
in a car accident
has drawn much public attention.
No one expected
that such an accident would bring
so many old cases to light.
Even the suicide case of Song Yucheng,
chairman of Dacheng Group,
who was under criminal investigation
for illegal business operations
10 years ago,
has been reopened.
Facts have proven
that Song Yucheng was indeed framed
by Wending Group back then.
It makes one sigh
at the unpredictability
of life.
Truth may be late,
but it is never absent.
Song Yanfei Wang Zhiyong (Wang Ruizi)
Shen Xi Xie Tiantian
Mu Liyan Chen Yongxia
Huang Fei (Huang Jing
Gao Yuhai
Forensic Doctor Cheng Gong
Zhao Wenjuan Li Ziying
Young Song Yanfei Chen Nuoyan
Investor Zha Minxin
Lead Singer Xu Weina
Wu Dalong Sui Dalong
Xiao Ze's Mother Zhao Yue'en
Guest Classmate Yue Yue
Yao Sha
Nanny Wang Chunyang
Girl Yingying Huang Mingfei
Xia Youzhen
Gao Yuhai's Secretary Du Du
Getaway Driver Liu Haohan
Old Man Walking Bird Wang Jiasheng
Waiter Liu Jiaqi Dai Guoming
Middle-aged Man Wang Xinda
Driver Old Zhao Wei Hong
Surveillance Police Qin Zhiqiang
Xiao Ze's Mother Pei Xiao
Young Man Tang Yuye
Receptionist Ren Jiefei
Mr. Zhao Liu Junjie
Scrapyard Boss Zhang Li Chenghu
Female Teacher Ai Li
Li Tianjun
Female Nurse Bai Wanting
Guo Xinye
Taxi Driver Bai Lei
Song Yucheng Liang Zhengchao
Forensic Doctor Zhou Wen Pei Xiao
Execution Doctor Sister Geng
Cleaner Liu Li
Hotpot Restaurant Owner Qin Haitao
Presenter Sui Dalong Yu Tianhang
Co-Presenter Feng
Chief Planner Li Meina
Chief Distributor Hu Kaichen
Executive Producer Peng Xia Kang Hairu
Script Planner Zhang Wanlu
Production Manager Liu Zhilong
Line Producer Hu Huazheng
Finance Geng Yusa
Set Assistant Xu Ganggang Zhao Menglin
Kitchen Manager Yin Xiumei
Li Zhiwei Ma Yuan
Wang Ji Zhang Xiong
Hu Lei Qiao Xueyue
Xiao Yucai Liu Xin
Co-Director Xu Yue
Director's Assistant Tang Yuye Li Gaoyang
On-set Assistant Director Liu Haohan
DIT Jin Linxin
Sound Director Zhang Kai
Art Director Zhao Daqian
Co-Art Director Gong Xue
Deputy Art Director Wang Tianyi
Props Director Yang Xueshan
On-set Supervisor Li Yao
Props Set Dresser Zhang Li Zhang Qingzhong
Camera Crew
A-Camera Focus Puller Yao Yonglei
B-Camera Operator Zhao Shidian
C-Camera Focus Puller Xie Xiaozhong
Lighting Director Gao Yun
Wardrobe & Makeup Supervisor Ma Yi
On-set Hair & Makeup Supervisor Li Zixu
On-set Wardrobe Supervisor
Zhang Lei Yi Junli
Beijing This Is Cola
Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Media Manager Yue Yue
Post-Production
Post-Production Coordinator Zhang Xiaoman
Re-recording Mixer Zhang Kai
Zhang Xinyu
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
VFX Executive: Jin Linxin
Compositors: Gao Dong, Wu Yingjie
Beijing Landuo Music
Music Director: Xiao Zhuang
Guitarist
Score Mixing: Zhao Yi
Composer: Xiao Zhuang
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
Yu Xiaotong
Lyricist: Bai Yuxiang
Arranger: Xiao Zhuang
Vocals: Ben Damiao
Gao Jingman
Vocals: Xu Yue
"Half a Beat Slow"
Composer: Xu
Producer: Xu Yue
"The More We Love, The More We Err"
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
"Only You" (Russian)
Lyricist: Bai Yuxiang
Publicity Department of
Shiyan Municipal Party Committee
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Hubei Zhi Yuxuan Agricultural
Technology Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Xiaowujia Catering Management
Hubei Zesheng Property Management
Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Maojian District Sunshine
Dance Art Training School
Shiyan Haishuo Loading and Unloading
Machinery Co., Ltd.
Exclusive Social Media Platform:
Weibo
Beijing Sui Brothers Film and Television
Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Co-production Companies
Shanxi Chengyi Film and Television
Media Co., Ltd.
Qinghe (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.